[upbeat rock music]
- It's really cool of your parents to have
a summer theater program at Get Sporty this year.
- I know, and "The Wonderful Wizard of Oz"
is my all-time favorite.
I mean, I've always wanted to play the role of Dorothy.
- I don't get it. Who's gonna come
to a theater in a sports store?
- Zip it, Franco.
- Now, now, theater and sports go together.
After all, theater is the-- [imitates swishing sound]
毕竟，剧院是——[模仿挥动声]
sport of the soul. - Yeah!
灵魂的运动。 - 对！
Oh, yeah. Get Sporty doesn't just support drama on the field,
哦，是的。Get Sporty不仅支持场上的戏剧，
we also support drama on the stage.
我们也支持舞台上的戏剧。
- Or a real theater was too expensive to rent out this year.
- 或者今年租用真正的剧院太贵了。
- Zip it, Franco.
- 闭嘴，弗兰科。
- Okay, well for anyone who wants to audition,
- 好吧，对于任何想要试镜的人，
the sign-up sheets are right here.
报名表就在这里。
- Oh, yeah.
- 哦，是的。
Dawn Harper for Dorothy,
Dawn Harper 饰演 Dorothy，
the role I was born to play.
我生来就是要演这个角色的。
Boom.
砰。
- I'm signing up for the good witch.
我要报名演好女巫。
I'll hold my boom until I get it.
我会保持我的砰直到我得到它。
- I wanna be a winged monkey.
我想演带翅膀的猴子。
Some people think they're scary.
有些人觉得它们很吓人。
But I think they're cute.
但我觉得它们很可爱。
- I'm gonna sign up to be the director.
我要报名当导演。
I like power, not fame.
我喜欢权力，不是名声。
- Miles, what are you gonna do?
迈尔斯，你打算做什么？
- I don't know. On the one hand,
- 我不知道。一方面，
I could play a tree.
我可以扮演一棵树。
But on the other hand, I could just
但另一方面，我也可以
sell popcorn during the show.
在演出期间卖爆米花。
I just can't decide. - You always make
我就是无法决定。- 你总是能
the right decision.
做出正确的决定。
- But I'm gonna go with the tree.
- 但我打算选择树。
- Huh.
- 嗯。
- Popcorn it is.
- 那就卖爆米花吧。
- So, boys, who are you auditioning for?
- 那么，男孩们，你们要试镜哪个角色？
- Sorry, Mom. This play thing really isn't our thing.
- Well, I am psyched for it. I mean, ever since I was a little girl, I've always dreamt of playing Dorothy.
[inhales sharply] Just like Ericka Knightly.
The best Dorothy ever.
- Thank you. - Oh, you're welcome.
Whoa, whoa, that was Ericka Knightly!
- It still is.
- Oh, my gosh. I love you.
- I worship you. - I live for you.
- I have a picture of you in my pocket.
- Ahh, "Sudden Mom." 'Twas an instant hit.
- 啊，《突然妈妈》。那真是一炮而红。
- I can't believe you're really here.
- 真不敢相信你真的在这里。
- So what's a big star like you doing back in Boulder?
- 像你这样的大明星怎么会回到博尔德来？
- Well, we were gonna surprise you kids,
- 嗯，我们本来想给你们一个惊喜，
but Ericka is gonna be our guest director.
- 但埃里卡将成为我们的客座导演。
[all exclaim]
[众人惊叹]
- You told her the theater was in a sporting goods store
- 你告诉她剧院在一个体育用品店里，
and she still came?
- 她还是来了？
- Young man, I don't know you.
- 年轻人，我不认识你。
But theater is the sport of the soul.
- 但剧院是灵魂的运动。
- Ah! [laughs]
- 啊！[笑]
I was just making that up. - So good.
我刚才只是随口说说。 - 太好了。
- I came back to stage the finest production
- 我回来是为了上演这部小镇从未见过的最精彩的
of "The Wonderful Wizard of Oz" this town has ever seen.
《绿野仙踪》。
Well, since my production.
嗯，自从我的那次演出之后。
I didn't just play Dorothy. I was Dorothy.
我不只是扮演多萝西。我就是多萝西。
Anybody else just get a shiver?
有人感到一阵寒意吗？
- Shiver, Franco.
- 寒意，弗兰科。
- Ah, well, look at you four.
- 啊，看看你们四个。
The perfect Dorothy, Tin Woodman,
完美的多萝西、铁皮人、
Scarecrow, Cowardly Lion.
稻草人，胆小的狮子。
Oh, and you've even got yourself a little Toto.
哦，你甚至还有自己的小托托。
Air pet.
空气宠物。
You know, you could be discovered in this production.
你知道，你可能会在这部作品中被发现。
Just like I was. - Ah, oh, my brothers
就像我一样。 - 哦，我的兄弟们 - 不参加试镜。 - 是的，我们参加。
aren't auditioning. - Yes, we are.
- 完全是我们的风格。 - 让我做你的托托。
- Totally our thing. - Make me your Toto.
- 来吧，Ericka，我们带你参观剧院。
- Come on, Ericka, we'll show you the theater.
- 试镜时见。
- I'll see you at the auditions.
- 等不及了！ - 再见！
- Can't wait! - Bye!
- 再见！
- Bye!
再见！
- But I thought you guys weren't auditioning.
但我以为你们不打算试镜。
- Well, that was before she said we could become famous.
嗯，那是在她说我们可以成名之前。
- Oh, I think she was talking to me.
哦，我觉得她是在跟我说话。
I mean, she got discovered playing Dorothy.
我是说，她就是在扮演多萝西时被发现的。
And so will I.
我也会的。
- [laughs] Not if I have anything to do with it.
（笑）如果我有任何发言权的话，你就不会。
- Oh, no.
哦，不。
It's Rose Dirken.
是罗斯·迪肯。
- She gets the lead in every play she tries out for.
她每次试镜都能得到主角。
- And now, I'm auditioning for Dorothy.
- 现在，我要试镜多萝西。
- Boom.
- 砰。
- Finally, some drama in a sporting goods store.
- 终于，在体育用品店里有点戏剧性了。
all: Zip it, Franco!
大家都说：闭嘴，弗兰科！
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ 啦, 啦, 啦, 啦, 啦, 啦, 啦, 啦, 啦, 啦, 啦 ♪
- This is bad, for if the Wicked Witch enchants us,
这很糟糕，因为如果邪恶女巫对我们施了魔法，
she will make us all her slaves.
她会把我们都变成她的奴隶。
- And then I shall get no brains.
那样我就得不到智慧了。
- And I shall get no courage.
那样我就得不到勇气了。
- And I shall get no heart.
那样我就得不到心了。
- And I shall get no shot at beating Rose Dirken
那样我就没有机会打败罗斯·迪肯
if my brothers can't act.
如果我的兄弟们不能表演的话。
- Okay, you need to relax.
好吧，你需要放松。
You're putting way too much pressure on yourself.
你给自己施加了太大的压力。
- Yeah. And us.
是的，还有我们。
- That's because we need to be perfect.
那是因为我们需要做到完美。
You know, like Ericka. You heard her,
你知道，就像Ericka那样。你听到了，
she didn't just play Dorothy.
她不仅仅是扮演Dorothy。
She was Dorothy.
她就是Dorothy。
She had the perfect hair, the perfect dress,
她有完美的发型，完美的裙子，
the perfect shoes.
完美的鞋子。
Wait. That's--that's it.
等等。就是这样。
That's how I'll get this role.
这就是我得到这个角色的方法。
I'll be Dorothy! - Dawn--
我要成为Dorothy！
- Dorothy. - Weird.
- 多萝西。 - 奇怪。
- Okay, the only way you're going to be Dorothy
- 好吧，你想要成为多萝西的唯一方法
is by rehearsing.
就是通过排练。
So let's pick this up
所以让我们从这个
with the Tin Woodman's big dance solo.
铁皮人的大型舞蹈独奏开始。
I've just been oiled. And a one and a two--
我刚上了油。一、二——
- Oh, yeah, good idea! Here, you guys
- 哦，对，好主意！来，你们
need some more rehearsing.
还需要多排练。
And in the meantime, Dorothy is off
与此同时，多萝西正要去
to see Dawn's closet.
看看Dawn的衣橱。
- Weirder.
更奇怪了。
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
- Okay, so in this scene,
好的，在这个场景中，
your house has just landed on the Wicked Witch.
你的房子刚刚落在邪恶女巫身上。
- Whose house?
谁的房子？
- Dorothy's. And as the Good Witch, I say to you--
多萝西的。作为善良女巫，我对你们说——
- What's my name? - Dorothy!
我的名字是什么？
Welcome to the Land of the Munchkins.
欢迎来到芒奇金人的国度。
And Dorothy says--
多萝西说——
- Yes! In the basket you go.
是的！你进篮子里去。
- You're not talking about Toto.
你说的不是托托。
You're shopping online again.
你又在网购了。
- But I have everything else.
但我其他东西都有了。
You know, the hair, the dress, the dog.
你知道的，头发，裙子，还有狗。
I just need these sparkly, silver shoes.
我只是需要这双闪亮的银鞋。
- Those are a size 12, triple E.
那双是12码，三倍E。
That's a scary Dorothy.
那是个吓人的多萝西。
- Well I can fit shoes inside the shoes, you know?
嗯，我可以在鞋子里再放鞋子，你知道吗？
Oh, see. Here's a size ten Cowardly Lion's foot.
哦，看。这里有一只10码的胆小狮子的脚。
It'll slip right in.
它会直接滑进去。
- Forget the shoes. If you don't know the lines,
别管鞋子了。如果你不知道台词，
Rose Dirkin's gonna get the part
罗丝·迪金会得到这个角色，
and the shoes aren't going to matter.
鞋子也就无所谓了。
- Ooh, size ten Cowardly Lion's feet.
噢，十码胆小狮子的脚。
A little big, but I can wear a shoe inside it
有点大，但我可以在里面再穿一双鞋。
Size eight Tin Woodman's. - Ooh, size eight Tin Woodman's.
八码铁皮伐木工的。
- Does anyone wanna rehearse?
噢，八码铁皮伐木工的。
- We've been rehearsing all morning.
有人想排练吗？
We know our lines.
我们整个早上都在排练。我们知道我们的台词。
- Yeah, if you wanna worry about someone,
- 是的，如果你想担心某人，
worry about Dawn.
担心Dawn。
- Who? - You!
- 谁？ - 你！
You're not Dorothy because if you don't rehearse,
你不是Dorothy，因为如果你不排练，
you are never going to be Dorothy!
你永远也不会成为Dorothy！
- Yeah, well, I'm never going to be Dorothy
- 是的，好吧，我永远不会成为Dorothy
unless I am Dorothy.
除非我是Dorothy。
And I am not Dorothy without
而且没有那些闪亮的银鞋，我就不是Dorothy。
those sparkly, silver shoes.
- 相信我，Ericka是个认真的演员。
- Trust me, Ericka's a serious actor.
她最后才会注意到你的鞋子。
The last thing she's gonna notice is your shoes.
她最后注意到的肯定不会是你的鞋子。
- Maybe you're right.
也许你是对的。
- Ahh, look at you!
啊，看看你！
You are Dorothy.
你就是多萝西。
Well, except for those shoes.
嗯，除了那些鞋子。
That's the first thing I noticed.
那是我首先注意到的。
- Oh, I've been online all day, but I just can't find any that are as perfect as yours.
哦，我整天都在网上找，但就是找不到像你那样的完美鞋子。
- Oh, well, honey, if you want shoes
哦，亲爱的，如果你想找
that actually were mine, check out
真正属于我的鞋子，去看看
Julie and Julie's Costume Shop.
朱莉和朱莉的服装店。
That's where I donate all of my old show clothes.
那就是我捐赠所有旧演出服装的地方。
Air hugs, air hugs, air hugs, air hugs, air hugs.
空中拥抱，空中拥抱，空中拥抱，空中拥抱，空中拥抱。
- Did you guys hear that? Problem solved.
你们听到了吗？问题解决了。
Here. You guys rehearse while I go get the shoes.
你们在这里排练，我去拿鞋子。
- Dawn, she said the four of us are perfect.
Dawn，她说我们四个人很完美。
If you don't get your part, we might not get our parts.
如果你没得到你的角色，我们可能也得不到我们的角色。
- Dawn, let the guys go get the shoes.
Dawn，让男生们去拿鞋子吧。
You need to rehearse.
你需要排练。
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不，不。
I cannot trust them to not let me down.
我不能信任他们，他们可能会让我失望。
- Name one time we've let you down.
- 举一个我们让你失望的例子。
- Number 106.
- 第106次。
The time I asked for string cheese but instead--
那次我想要绳状奶酪，结果你们...
- Fine! - We get it.
- 好吧！ - 我们知道了。
- Let us make it up to you.
- 让我们弥补你。
- Yeah, we'll go to Julie and Julie's
- 对，我们会去Julie和Julie的店
and bring you the best pair of string cheese.
给你带回最好的绳状奶酪。
- Shoes, Dicky.
- 鞋子，Dicky。
- Really?
- 真的吗？
- Yeah. - All right, shoes.
- 是的。 - 好吧，鞋子。
- Look, Dawn, we want these parts just as badly as you do.
- 看，Dawn，我们和你一样迫切需要这些部件。
Trust us. We won't let you down.
相信我们。我们不会让你失望的。
Fine. Please get the shoes. - Don't worry. We will.
好吧。请去拿鞋子。 - 别担心。我们会去的。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
Not if Rose Dirken gets them first.
但如果Rose Dirken先拿到它们就不好了。
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
- Great. Julie and Julie are closed for lunch.
- 太好了。Julie和Julie去吃午饭了。
- I wonder what they're having.
- 不知道他们在吃什么。
- Who cares? As soon as they open back up,
- 谁在乎呢？他们一开门，
we'll get those shoes and get back to Dawn.
我们会拿到那些鞋子，然后回去找Dawn。
Just stay focused.
保持专注。
- I bet it's avocado toast.
- 我打赌是鳄梨吐司。
Hipsters.
潮人。
- Dicky! - Sorry. Right.
- 迪基！ - 对不起。对。
We're not gonna get distracted.
我们不会分心的。
[bell dinging]
[铃声叮当]
[romantic rock music]
[浪漫摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
- Whoa. - Yeah.
- 哇。 - 是啊。
- Hi, boys. - Hey, lollipop.
- 嗨，男孩们。 - 嘿，棒棒糖。
Where'd you get that Rose?
你从哪儿弄到那朵玫瑰的？
- Oh, at For Suckers Only, right across the street.
- 哦，在'只给傻瓜'，就在街对面。
There's only three left. Bye.
只剩下三朵了。再见。
- Guys, there's only three left.
- 伙计们，只剩下三朵了。
And there's-- wait, one, two three--
而且这里有——等等，一，二，三——
three of us! [cell phone rings]
我们有三个人！[手机铃声响起]
- Oh, it's Dawn. - Don't let her distract us.
- 哦，是Dawn。 - 别让她分散我们的注意力。
- Good thinking. Ignore.
- 好主意。忽略。
- They ignored me! - Can we just rehearse?
- 他们无视我！ - 我们能排练一下吗？
- They completely ignored me. - I know how that feels.
- 他们完全忽视了我。 - 我懂那种感觉。
- Do you have any idea how that feels?
- 你知道那是什么感觉吗？
♪ ♪
- Oh, there were way more than three lollipops in there.
- 哦，那里面的棒棒糖远不止三个。
- That Rose Dirken, not very smart.
- 那个Rose Dirken，不太聪明。
[bell dings]
[铃声响起]
- [laughs]
- [笑]
In your face, suckers. [laughs]
在你们脸上，笨蛋们。[笑]
- Or she's wicked smart.
- 或者她非常聪明。
- That place was for suckers only.
- 那个地方只适合笨蛋。
And we're the suckers.
而我们就是那些傻瓜。
- This is not good. Without those shoes,
- 这不太妙。没有那些鞋子，
Dawn's confidence will be shot
黎明的自信会大受打击
and she'll blow her audition.
她会搞砸她的试镜。
- Hold on. Dawn doesn't know Rose Dirken has the shoes.
- 等等。黎明不知道罗斯·迪肯有那些鞋子。
Do you still have that stupid bedazzle kit?
你还有那个傻乎乎的装饰工具包吗？
- First of all, it's not stupid.
- 首先，那不傻。
And secondly, it's not a kit. It's an eight piece pro set
其次，那不是一个工具包。那是一个八件套专业套装
with a precision hook attachment
带有精确钩附件
for those hard to dazzle areas.
用于那些难以装饰的区域。
- Do you have it or not? - Of course I do.
- 你还有那个吗？ - 当然有。
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, hey, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, hey, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- Why aren't they here? Our audition is in five minutes!
- 他们怎么还没到？我们的试镜还有五分钟就开始了！
Pick up, pick up!
接电话，接电话！
- Hi, Dawn. - Finally! Where are you?
- 嗨，Dawn。 - 终于！你在哪儿？
- Right behind you.
- 就在你后面。
- Oh!
- 哦！
- Here you go. - The sparkly, silver shoes.
- 给你。 - 闪亮的银色鞋子。
- Totally them.
- 绝对是它们。
- Yes! Wow, thank you.
- 是的！哇，谢谢你。
- No problem. - Happy to help.
- 没问题。 - 乐意帮忙。
- We're the best.
- 我们是最好的。
- Do you think she'll figure out the shoes are fake?
- 你觉得她会发现鞋子是假的吗？
- With Ricky's shoe dazzling? Heh, I don't think so.
- 有瑞奇的鞋子闪耀吗？嘿，我不这么认为。
- All right, Harpers, you're up.
- 好了，哈珀家的人，轮到你们了。
- Ah, I see you've got them.
- 啊，我看到你拿到了。
Nice touch.
- 很棒的点子。
Here we go. Now, just relax, have fun.
- 我们开始了。现在，放松，享受乐趣。
I'll cue you.
- 我会提示你。
[clears throat]
- [清嗓子]
Why do you stand before the Wizard?
你为何站在巫师面前？
- I'm here for courage. - I'm here for a heart. - I'm here for a brain.
- 我来寻求勇气。 - 我来寻求一颗心。 - 我来寻求智慧。
- And I'm here to get back to Kansas
- 而我来是为了回到堪萨斯。
because there's no place like ham.
因为没有什么地方比得上火腿。
- Did you say ham?
- 你刚才说火腿？
- Um, Ericka, do you think I could try that one more time?
- 呃，埃里卡，你觉得我能再试一次吗？
- Of course.
- 当然可以。
- I'm here to get back to Kansas
- 我来是为了回到堪萨斯。
because there's no place like home.
因为没有什么地方比得上家。
Not ham.
不是火腿。
- Nice save.
救场不错。
- And Dorothy says--
然后多萝西说——
- Oh! Oh, yeah. Uh, right. Uh, the--the--
哦！哦，对。呃，对。呃，那——那——
take me back to Auntie Em! [laughs]
带我回到艾玛姨妈那里！[笑]
- What? - Oh, no.
什么？
- The glue must not be dry.
哦，不。
- Next up, Rose Dirken.
接下来，罗斯·迪肯。
- [laughs]
[笑]
Ohh. Nice shoes.
哦，鞋子不错。
- What did you do?
你做了什么？
♪
- No, you can't do this!
不，你不能这样做！
You can't cast Rose Dirken as Dorothy.
你不能让Rose Dirken扮演Dorothy。
You said I was perfect for that part.
你说过我是那个角色的完美人选。
I mean, of course it wasn't my best work--
我的意思是，当然那不是我最好的表现——
- You said there's no place like ham.
你说过的，没有地方像火腿那样。
- Um, actually, no I didn't.
呃，实际上，我没说过。
I said there's no place like home.
我说的是没有地方像家那样。
I just said it with an Australian accent.
我只是用澳大利亚口音说的。
You know, like, g'day mate, there's no place like ham.
你知道，就像，g'day mate，没有地方像火腿那样。
I made a choice. - So did I.
我做了一个选择。 - 我也是。
Rose Dirken.
罗斯·迪肯。
- Ooh, burn!
- 哦，真糟糕！
- [sighs] Look, Dawn,
- [叹气] 听着， Dawn，
I know what it's like to not get a part.
我知道得不到角色的感觉。
- Really? - No. Now, that was acting.
- 真的吗？ - 不，那只是演戏。
But I can see you're disappointed.
但我看得出你很失望。
And I would hate for there to be bad feelings between us.
我不想我们之间有不好的感觉。
So here, air hug it out?
所以，来个空气拥抱化解一下？
- Sorry, Ericka, I'm really not in the mood for air hugs.
- 抱歉， Ericka，我真的没心情空气拥抱。
I'd love for you to be a winged monkey.
我希望你能扮演一只飞猴。
- Number 107.
第107号。
Fake shoes!
假鞋！
I cannot believe you guys ruined my audition.
我真不敢相信你们毁了我的试镜。
- Well, it wasn't a complete disaster.
嗯，这还不是一场彻底的灾难。
I mean, we got the parts we wanted.
我的意思是，我们得到了我们想要的那些角色。
- Yeah, and I would've gotten the part I wanted, too,
是啊，我本来也能得到我想要的角色，
if you would've just gotten me the shoes
如果你能给我弄来那双鞋
instead of these!
而不是这些的话！
- How are you standing?
你怎么站得住？
- I am that mad!
- 我真的很生气！
Plus, I'm leaning on Armond's chair. Sorry.
而且，我正靠在Armond的椅子上。抱歉。
Ugh! Could this day get any worse?
啊！这一天还能更糟吗？
First, my brothers let me down, then Ericka lets me down.
先是我的兄弟们让我失望，然后Ericka也让我失望。
Everybody's letting me down.
每个人都在让我失望。
- Dawn, I think you're the only one
- Dawn，我觉得唯一让你失望的人
who let you down. - Oh, snap!
是你自己。 - 哦，天哪！
- We tried to tell you you needed to rehearse more.
- 我们试图告诉你你需要多练习。
But you were just so obsessed with those shoes.
但你就是对那些鞋子太着迷了。
- You're right. Look, it doesn't matter anyway.
- 你说得对。看，反正也没关系。
It's just a play and Ericka's just a person.
这只是一出戏，而Ericka也只是一个普通人。
I mean, I'm not upset about it.
我是说，我并没有因此感到沮丧。
In fact, I'm fine with it
实际上，我对这事儿挺无所谓的。
- Really? - No. That was acting!
真的吗？不，那只是演戏！
I am devastated and miserable!
我感到非常崩溃和痛苦！
- Wow. Where was that during her audition?
哇，那她在试镜时怎么没表现出来？
- I don't know. Maybe she left it at ham.
我不知道，也许她当时没把这部分发挥出来。
- Is there anything more exciting
还有什么比剧院活起来更令人兴奋的吗？
than a theater coming to life?
演员们，道具师，还有那个家伙在忙什么。
Actors, prop masters, whatever that guy's doing.
好吧，我知道这不是你原本计划的，但和父母一起在后台工作也挺有趣的。
- Okay, I know it's not what you had planned,
好吧，我知道这不是你原本计划的，
but it is kinda fun, working backstage with your parents.
但和父母一起在后台工作，确实挺有趣的。
Right, girlfriend? - Sure, Mom friend.
对吧，女朋友？当然，妈妈的朋友。
- Okay, now, on Ericka's cue,
好了，现在，在Ericka的提示下，
you're gonna slowly let out this rope
你要慢慢地放出这条绳子，
and it'll lower the cardboard house, okay?
这样纸板房子就会慢慢降下来，明白吗？
Here you go. All right?
给你。好了吗？
Now, can you handle this while I try to find
现在，你能处理这个，同时我去找
another peg for this tornado rope?
另一根固定龙卷风绳的钉子吗？
- Uh, sure. - Great.
呃，当然。很好。
- There's a storm coming, Toto.
- 托托，暴风雨要来了。
Quick, run...
快跑...
home.
回家。
- Quick, run home.
- 快跑回家。
Yeah, that's what the audience is gonna say
是的，观众一旦看到你的表演，就会这么说。
once they see your performance. [laughs]
[笑]
Yes! Good one, Dawn.
没错！说得好，Dawn。
Self high five.
自己给自己击个掌。
[gasps] - [screaming, thud]
[吸气声] - [尖叫声，砰]
- Ahh!
- 啊！
- Somebody get this monstrosity off of me!
有人快把这个怪物从我身上弄走！
- I am so sorry!
我非常抱歉！
- Did you drop it on her so you could play Dorothy?
你是不是故意把它掉在她身上，好扮演多萝西？
- No, of course not! It was a total accident, I swear.
不，当然不是！我发誓，这完全是个意外。
- You should wear this witch's hat.
你应该戴上这个女巫帽。
It's for witches.
这是给女巫戴的。
'Cause you're witchy.
因为你有点像女巫。
- I didn't do it on purpose.
我不是故意的。
You guys gotta believe me.
你们得相信我。
I'm not witchy.
我不是女巫。
[shimmering tone]
♪ ♪
[percussive music]
Squishy...
软软的...
we are so not in Boulder right now.
我们现在绝对不在博尔德。
♪ ♪
- What is this place?
- 这是什么地方？
I mean, it looks like Boulder, but bolder.
我的意思是，这里看起来像博尔德，但更大胆。
And why am I dressed like Dorothy?
而且为什么我穿得像多萝西？
Oh, well, except for these fake shoes my brothers made me.
哦，除了这些我兄弟们逼我穿的假鞋。
Hey, at least they're not here.
嘿，至少他们不在这里。
Ahh! They're here.
啊！他们来了。
- You know, if I had a heart, that would really hurt.
你知道，如果我有心的话，那真的会很痛。
[metal clanging]
[金属碰撞声]
- Wait, where am I?
等等，我在哪儿？
- Uh, Oz. And I thought I was the one with no brains.
呃，奥兹国。我还以为我是那个没脑子的人呢。
- Wait, how did I get here?
等等，我是怎么来到这里的？
- You were blown here by a big tomato.
你被一个大番茄吹到这里来的。
- I think you mean tornado.
我想你是指龙卷风。
- You say tornado, I say tomato.
你说龙卷风，我说番茄。
- Wait, how did you guys get here?
等等，你们是怎么来到这里的？
- Don't ask us. It's your dream.
别问我们。这是你的梦。
- Wait, a dream?
等等，一个梦？
But this all feels so real.
但这感觉都太真实了。
- Ah!
啊！
- Oh, but it is real.
哦，但这是真的。
- You know, you could warn a lion.
你知道，你可以提醒一下那只狮子。
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Mae?
哇，哇，哇。梅？
Okay, look, I am really confused right now.
好吧，听着，我现在真的很困惑。
But before I ask any questions,
但在我问任何问题之前，
that dress is fantastic!
那件裙子真是太棒了！
- Ah, I know, right?
- 啊，我知道，对吧？
It's good to be the Good Witch.
成为好女巫真是太好了。
Now say hello to all my Munchkin friends.
现在向我的所有芒奇金朋友们问好。
[overlapping cheering, chatter]
[重叠的欢呼声，嘈杂声]
- You flying in here was so cool.
- 你飞进来的样子太酷了。
- Yeah, your house flipped five times.
- 是的，你的房子翻转了五次。
- I'm adding that to my routine.
- 我要把这个加到我的表演里。
- This is Twisty and her Gold Medal Girls.
- 这是Twisty和她的金牌女孩们。
They're always flipping out about something.
他们总是为某事激动不已。
- We're passionate.
- 我们充满热情。
Now that you know who we are,
既然你已经知道我们是谁了，
who are you?
你是谁呢？
- Well, what do you mean? I'm Dorothy.
- 嗯，你指的是什么？我是多萝西。
- [scoffs] Not in those shoes.
- [嗤之以鼻] 穿着那样的鞋子可不像。
- Yeah, those are nasty.
- 是啊，那些鞋子真糟糕。
- Oh, uh, these are just my travelling shoes.
- 哦，呃，这些只是我的旅行鞋。
Uh--my real ones are over there.
呃——我真正的鞋子在那边。
BRB!
马上回来！
- Those shoes are just cheap knock-offs.
那些鞋子只是廉价的仿冒品。
- Looks like they were made by a wannabe dazzler.
看起来像是某个想成为炫目者的人做的。
- You know what? That would've really hurt
你知道吗？如果我有心的话，那会真的很伤人。
if I had a heart. [metal clangs]
看到了吗？我的鞋子就在这里
- See? My shoes are right here
在另一个人的脚上。
on this other person's feet.
看到了吗？[笑]我是多萝西。
See? [laughs] I'm Dorothy.
不，我是多萝西。
- No, I'm Dorothy.
两个多萝西？
- Two Dorothys?
等等，发生了什么事？
- Wait, wait, what's going on?
是时候唱首歌了。
- It's time to break into a song.
- It happens a lot around here.
- ♪ If you were Dorothy, you wouldn't be confused ♪
♪ I'm Dorothy, so won't you give me back my shoes, yeah ♪
- ♪ I'm Dorothy this time ♪
♪ I win and you lose ♪
♪ Yes, you do ♪ - ♪ No, I don't ♪
- ♪ Yes, you do ♪ both: ♪ I--I--I'm Dorothy ♪
- ♪ Are you sure? ♪ - ♪ She looks mad ♪
- ♪ The shoes don't look so bad ♪
- ♪ Yes they do they're just fakes ♪
♪ What's up with your mistakes?
♪ I'm Dorothy, I'm sure it's me, can't you see? ♪
- ♪ No, it's me ♪ - ♪ No, it's me ♪
- ♪ Obviously ♪ both: ♪ I--I--I'm Dorothy ♪
♪ D-O-R-O-T-H-Y ♪
- ♪ That's my name so don't you try to be me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the real Dorothy ♪
both: ♪ D-O-R-O-T-H-Y ♪
- ♪ Why don't you stop living that lie ♪
- ♪ I don't need to tell you why ♪
♪ 我不需要告诉你为什么 ♪
♪ I'm Dorothy, I'm Dorothy ♪
♪ 我是多萝西，我是多萝西 ♪
- ♪ I hear your words but they make no sense to me ♪
♪ 我听到你的话，但它们对我毫无意义 ♪
♪ 'Cause we all know that I'm the real Dorothy ♪
♪ 因为我们都知道我是真正的多萝西 ♪
- ♪ I've got the clothes and the hair and the dress ♪
♪ 我有衣服、头发和裙子 ♪
- ♪ And my shoes ♪ - ♪ They're my shoes ♪
♪ 还有我的鞋子 ♪ ♪ 它们是我的鞋子 ♪
- ♪ Dorothy's shoes, - I--I--I'm Dorothy ♪
♪ 多萝西的鞋子，我——我——我是多萝西 ♪
♪ There ain't no stopping ♪
♪ 没有人能阻止 ♪
♪ This is my destiny ♪
♪ 这是我的命运 ♪
♪ I was born to be Dorothy, yeah ♪
♪ 我生来就是要成为多萝西，是的 ♪
- ♪ Were you born to forget that it's me? ♪
♪ 你生来就忘了我是谁吗？ ♪
- ♪ No, it's me ♪ - ♪ Um, it's me ♪
♪ 不，是我 ♪ ♪ 嗯，是我 ♪
- ♪ It's so me ♪ both: ♪ I--I--I'm Dorothy ♪
♪ 这就是我 ♪ ♪ 我——我——我是多萝西 ♪
♪ D-O-R-O-T-H-Y ♪
- ♪ That's my name so don't you try to be me ♪
♪ 那是我的名字 ♪ ♪ 所以你别想成为我 ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the real Dorothy ♪ - ♪ I'm Dorothy ♪
♪ 因为我是真正的多萝西 ♪ ♪ 我是多萝西 ♪
both: ♪ D-O-R-O-T-H-Y ♪
♪ D-O-R-O-T-H-Y ♪
- ♪ Why don't you stop living that lie ♪
♪ 你为何不停下 ♪ ♪ 活在那个谎言里 ♪
- ♪ I don't need to tell you why ♪
♪ 我不需要 ♪ ♪ 告诉你为什么 ♪
both: ♪ I'm Dorothy ♪
♪ 我是多萝西 ♪
- Wait, so which one's Dorothy?
- 等等，哪个才是多萝西？
- Yeah, that song taught us nothing.
- 是啊，那首歌什么也没说明。
- I guess the only thing now we can do is--
- 我猜我们现在只能——
both: Flip out!
- 两个一起：发疯吧！
- Okay, give me those shoes.
- 好了，把那鞋子给我。
- Here!
- 给你！
- What do we do now? - Throw them back!
- 现在怎么办？- 扔回去！
- Wait! Don't you want these lollipops first?
- 等等！你们不想先要这些棒棒糖吗？
[both scoff] - Come on.
[两人轻蔑声] - 得了吧。
We're not suckers.
我们又不是傻瓜。
- Well, of course you're not.
哦，你们当然不是。
Here, let me have these while you unwrap those.
来，把这些给我，你们去拆那些。
- Thank you. - Very kind of you.
- 谢谢你。- 你真好。
- Very kind of you, suckers.
- 你们真好，傻瓜们。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- It's the Wicked Witch!
- 是邪恶女巫！
- Thanks for the shoes, boys.
- 谢谢你们的鞋子，孩子们。
- We thought you were Rose!
- 我们以为你是罗丝！
- No, she's over there,
- 不，她在那边，
under my mannequin spell with the rest of them!
和其他人一样，中了我的模特咒语！
- Do you think Dawn saw any of that?
你觉得道恩看到那些了吗？
- Nah, she's frozen. She didn't see anything.
不，她冻住了。她什么都没看见。
- I saw everything!
我全看见了！
- Ahh! - Ah!
啊！- 啊！
And I know you're not frozen. - Yes, we are.
我知道你们没冻住。- 是的，我们冻住了。
- Can't move. - Totally frozen.
- 动不了。- 完全冻住了。
[slapping] [all exclaim]
[拍打声] [众人惊呼]
- Ow, oh.
- 哎哟，哦。
- Can I please have my shoes back?
- 能把我的鞋子还给我吗？
- No. And now it's time for me to poof out!
- 不行。现在是我消失的时候了！
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
- I can't believe you guys.
- 真不敢相信你们。
Once again, you let me down. Welcome to number 108.
又一次，你们让我失望了。欢迎来到第108次。
- Uh, in Oz, this is the first time we've let you down.
- 呃，在奥兹国，这是我们第一次让你失望。
So technically, this is number one.
所以严格来说，这是第一次。
- You know, if you're really a good witch,
- 你知道，如果你真是个好女巫，
you better hold me back.
你最好拦住我。
- Whoa!
- 哇！
♪ ♪
♪ I, I, I'm Dorothy ♪
♪ 我是，我是，我是多萝西 ♪
♪ D-O-R-O-T-H-Y ♪
- ♪ That's my name so don't you try to be me ♪
♪ 那就是我的名字，所以别试图成为我 ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the real Dorothy ♪
♪ 因为我是真正的多萝西 ♪
♪ D-O-R-O-T-H-Y ♪
- ♪ Why don't you stop living that lie ♪
♪ 你为何不停下，别再活在那谎言里 ♪
- ♪ I don't need to tell you why ♪
♪ 我不需要告诉你为什么 ♪
♪ I'm Dorothy, I'm Dorothy ♪
♪ 我是多萝西，我是多萝西 ♪
♪ D-O-R-O-T-H-Y ♪
- ♪ That's my name so don't you try to be me ♪
♪ 那就是我的名字，所以别试图成为我 ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the real Dorothy ♪ - ♪ I'm Dorothy ♪
♪ 因为我是真正的多萝西 ♪ ♪ 我是多萝西 ♪
♪ I'm Dorothy, I'm Dorothy ♪
♪ 我是多萝西，我是多萝西 ♪